featuredcustomers.com 2018-12-24

# FeaturedCustomers Privacy Policy

## Welcome to FeaturedCustomers.com!

We are really excited to have you visit our website and hope you make good use of our service, and, ultimately, that the experience of others by way of customer references, case studies, success stories, customer stories, and customer testimonials can lead you to making the right business software decision.

### Please read through this entire Privacy Policy thoroughly. We will work to keep this up to date.

## FEATUREDCUSTOMERS.COM PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy was last modified on October 1, 2015.

We are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and toward clarifying all usage of personal information.

You are being presented this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) because you are visiting a website (the “Website”) that is either (a) owned and operated by Software Prospect Inc. (“FeaturedCustomers.com”) or (b) includes content, including but not limited to registration and other forms, owned by SOFTWARE PROSPECT INC. or drawn from a website owned and operated by SOFTWARE PROSPECT INC. By accessing and using this Website or FeaturedCustomers.com services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and all other terms, policies and operating procedures that may be published on this Website. In addition, when you visit this Website or FeaturedCustomers.com and any of our participating business software providers’ ("Providers") websites, you are subject to both this Privacy Policy and any other terms of use and guidelines set forth at our Providers' websites. All these rules and policies are incorporated into this Privacy Policy by this reference. Please read this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms of Use and Conditions (“Terms”), and any Provider’s terms and conditions carefully. If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy or our Terms, do not enter or use this Website. We reserve the right to update or otherwise modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy periodically for changes and updates. Your use of this Website following posted change(s) and update(s) will be deemed an acceptance of such change(s).

SOFTWARE PROSPECT INC. operates https://www.featuredcustomers.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

  1. ### Information Collection and Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").

In an effort to provide you with assistance in deciding on the right business software for you, please be advised that FeaturedCustomers.com can and may pass on any information you fill out on any part of the Website to our Business Software Providers (“Providers”), including but not limited to your name, emails, phone numbers, physical addresses and information about your organization, including but not limited to name, industry, company revenue and company size, as well as information regarding your current software usage and software needs. In order for FeaturedCustomers.com and our Providers to further help you in your decision-making process, representatives of FeaturedCustomers.com and/or representatives of our Providers can and may reach out to you directly to talk about their products, services and/or promotions, which may include but is not limited to calling you, emailing you, and adding you to our newsletter. In addition, your information can and may be used for overall improvement of the Website, our customer service, our Providers’ services, and for the compiling and aggregating of statistics.

Our Website consists of customer references & reviews, customer testimonials, success stories, case studies, customer stories, and customer videos that will help you make the right purchasing decisions. This may include information about you, including but not limited to your name, photo, your LinkedIn ID, and the company you work for, as well as information about your organization, including the information aforementioned in the previous paragraph.

If you want to remove or change your personal information that is being displayed publicly on the Website under public pages, please send your request to info@featuredcustomers.com.

  2. ### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

  3. ### Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like most sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. First and Third party cookies do not store any FeaturedCustomers.com User Personal Information on the Website; they are simply identifiers. By continuing to use the Website, FeaturedCustomers.com Users consent to the placement of these cookies on their computing device in accordance with the terms above.

  4. ### Pixel Tracking

FeaturedCustomers.com may employ a common technique usually referred to as "pixel tracking" to measure the effectiveness of marketing and advertisements, as well as compile aggregate usage statistics. Pixel tracking, which may be used in connection with advertisements on other sites, on the Website or in email messages, involves the use of pixel tags (also known as "clear gifs," "Web beacons" or "1-by-1 gifs") that are not visible to the user of the site and consist of a few lines of computer coding. For example, if you visit the Website from an advertisement on another site or from social media, the pixel tag will reference the cookie you received when you clicked on the advertisement. The pixel tag also may register this activity with a business partner to allow us to count the number of times or when an advertisement is accessed. This data is collected for use in FeaturedCustomers.com’ marketing and research, as well as to inform our Providers on Website activity and user behavior. The pixels that are tracking activity can be provided by FeaturedCustomers.com, by our Providers, and/or third-party advertising, social media or websites. Personally identifiable information about you is not collected by pixel tracking, nor is any tracking information generated from the pixel tag allowed to be used for any other purpose other than to report Website activity to us.

  5. ### Third-party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve some or all of the advertisements you see on the Website. These advertisers, our Providers, and FeaturedCustomers.com itself can and may employ other pixels and cookies that collect information on your activity, however, this does not include what we deemed as personable identifiable information in Section 1 of this Privacy Policy.

  6. ### Policy Regarding Minors

FeaturedCustomers.com does not willingingly seek or collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age, in accordance with the U.S. Children Online Privacy and Protection Act.

  7. ### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

  8. ### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Website.

  9. ### Changes to Privacy Policy

FeaturedCustomers.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

If you have any further questions, please contact info@featuredcustomers.com.

PLEASE ALSO READ: FeaturedCustomers.com Terms of Use and Conditions.
